(Leonard:)Terrible.
(Leonard:)I worked really hard on that project.
(Leonard:)I stayed up all night singing
the clown's aria from Pagliacci...
(Leonard:)...to a lima bean sprout.
(Sheldon:)Go on.
(Leonard:)It wasn't my fault.
(Leonard:)I had never seen
my brother's project.
(Leonard:)And my mother could've told me
before...
(Leonard:)...instead of at the ceremony
in front of everyone.
(Sheldon:)So I hear you saying you're angry
with your mother.
(Leonard:)Damn right,
I'm angry with my mother.
[SNIFFLING]
(Leonard:)For God's sake,
I was 8 years old.
(Leonard:)She humiliated me.
(Leonard:)That's when the bed-wetting
started again.
(Sheldon:)-Thank you, Leonard.
-For what?
(Sheldon:)If someone as damaged as you
can find his way...
(Sheldon:)...to crawl out of bed each morning...
(Sheldon:)...I think I can face
a simple awards ceremony.